In this short course,
you saw a range of applications,
including processing customer reviews,
and building an
application to answer
questions over documents,
and even using an LLM
to decide when to make
a call to an external tool,
like web search,
to answer complex questions.
If a week or two ago,
someone had asked you,
how much work would it be to build
all of these applications?
I think a lot of people would have
thought, "Boy,
this sounds like weeks, you know,
maybe even longer of work.".
But you saw in this short course,
how with just a pretty
reasonable number of lines of code,
you can use LangChain
to build all of
these applications pretty efficiently.
As I hope you take these ideas,
maybe even take some
code snippets that you
saw in the Jupyter
Notebooks and use them
in your own applications.
And these ideas are
really just the start. There's
a lot of other
applications that you can
use language models for. These
models are so
powerful because they're applicable
to such a wide
range of tasks, whether it be answering questions
about CSVs, querying SQL
databases, interacting with
APIs.
There's a lot of different
examples of using chains
and the combinations of
prompts and output parsers
and then more chains
to do all these
things in LangChain. And
most of that is due
to the LangChain community. So
I want to also give
a really big thank out
to everyone in the community
who's contributed, whether it
be improvements in the documentation, making
it easier for others to
get started, or new
types of chains opening up a whole new
world of possibilities.
And so, with that,
if you have not yet already done so,
I hope you go to your laptop or
your desktop and run
pip install LangChain and
then go use this tool to go build
some amazing applications.